Right, so now we're going to start with the big form modeling.
Let's start with the neck. So I'm going to start off with something slightly darker
and then pick out the lighter shape in the middle. Okay, we're going to use for that.
Okay, we could use burnt umber but we're going to use the actual colors in the face.
So we're going to mix something up with this. Okay, so move some alizarin, green, yellow. Okay,
we're touching mid-yellow. So that's the red side. Neutralize that, more green.
I'm just going to test that. It's a bit lighter and a bit of light yellow. Okay, so something
around that, creation, the alizarin, green, and yellow. Don't want any light edges.
Just fix these edges. Nice come back in. So on one side it's burnt umber, like a burnt umber yellow.
On one side, side here. So if you need to shape that, come back in. Okay,
then to this mix, add a touch of so the mid-yellow to light yellow. Okay.
All right, so that's the neck. Now let's look at the the face. Okay, let's start with this.
Start with this shape here. It's going to get slightly darker. I'm going to run that down
some of that shape down the jawline. So that tone. Okay, use that as a transition maybe.
Okay, so it's quite red in there. That mix was using.
Maybe lover done it. A bit more on the red side.
We add some yellow into that. Just checking this. A bit too green. A bit more alizarin.
Too much alizarin. Come in back with a green. Touch of yellow.
Warm that up a bit. Just checking that tone somewhere around that. Think about
where that one comes up to just below the eye around there. Take it all the way up here.
And then it comes down there. Okay, then we're going to work up to the edge on the jawline.
That edge, the purple burnt umber. Right, so that's that. Now I'm going to look for
the tone. Okay, so I'm looking for something coming down this line. Okay, some kind of average
room. Gonna go with something around here. Say a bit more on the green side around the muzzle.
Okay, and then you can pick these darker shapes out after.
So I'm just looking for this for now. Something around that tone. Okay, so obviously
it's going to be some alizarin. All that some mid-green.
Gonna set that down yellow and check that. Something around there. Okay,
I think it's a bit greener on the muzzle. Now on the green side.
Here's my alizarin. Green, yellow. A bit more green or yellow. A bit more yellow in there.
Gonna check that jawline up a bit. It's just going to come back in.
That's okay. I'll just get a bit darker on the opposite side of the face there. Just a
bit of a darker version. This green darker. Okay, next I'm going to look for the
side plane shape. Actually before I get into that let's look for the temple. So temple is
that's going to be on the the green side. Okay, so look for the put something for that.
So maybe it's slightly lighter green. It's in a slightly lighter tone in the temple.
So it's kind of on the green side. It's going to be a variation of the alizarin.
This one green. I'm going to take this, soften that edge.
The red there comes up into it. Okay, soften the edge. Run into the hairline. That
hairline, that burnt temple. Okay, it's that kind of green shape. So this side,
gonna keep that green shape just a bit more alizarin.
Warm that up. A bit lighter than that. Okay, forehead. Something similar there.
Start off with the light.
And then the sun. That's in cabinet. Touch of white. That's in cabinet, such a white.
Thame brush. Bristle's good. Ultimate bristle. Okay, now we're gonna look for that highlight.
So if we're drawing that, then it's going to be something down here, across there.
Okay, we'll shape this highlight. After we can work into this, we'll just put something in.
Okay, just one side it. Got this plane here. A bit more red in there. So I can call that some
yellow, alizarin. A bit more on the yellow alizarin. Touch of green to neutralize that color.
That mark there. Okay, coming back with the temple. Okay, then up in here. This is all slightly darker.
Pin there. Run that hairline. Slightly warmer. Just put something around. It's like a lighter
version of that cheek. I've got some lighter yellow that might give me something that I'm looking for.
A shape kind of comes up to the, in line with the socket there, uses these shapes. Okay,
and you've got this tone coming up there. Slightly darker. All right, then across the forehead,
got this slightly lighter shape across here. Looks like there's a bit more yellow in there.
So I was using this tone here to lighten that up again. Okay, just thinking how this is working.
It's kind of connecting with all these shapes. Then that, come back in. Then some purple. Okay,
then kind of around the forehead for that lighter version. A bit more pink. Okay,
in this color, around here. We can go up to this, to the highlight, and then we're going to start
taking some of that painting. Start highlighting. Diffusing. So yeah, just working some,
starting to color that highlight. Very light tones in there. Just shaping these. Okay,
so there's the forehead. Now let's look for the front plane of the cheek. Okay, it's going to be on
the pink side. So some alizarin. Maybe some lighter alizarin. A green. It's on that down.
Going to pick out the front plane. And that's going to be something around here. Can be grouped
into the front plane. So just that, it's like a lighter version. Something around this
light version for the darker. So alizarin yellow. Going to add a touch of green,
just to take that down slightly. Maybe make that cheek a bit more pink,
a bit lower chroma. Just going to add a bit more alizarin yellow in there.
But yeah, just needing to pump that in there. Cheek a bit more redder. Okay, and that,
the big four modeling. The face. Just slightly lighter on this side.
Okay, yeah, so that's the big four modeling. Next is the ears, nose and mouth.